nettravel.com 2011-06-06

# Nettravel

| Privacy Policy  
---  
  
What we at NetTravel.com consider primary is your right to privacy. The guidelines we use to protect information, which we collect about you when you visit our website is cited very clearly in our privacy policy.  

Information we collect   
What we do with this information   
The use of "cookies"   
Your consent   
   
Information we collect   
  
At different point in time, NetTravel.com requires personal information. This can be done while visiting the site, or during a purchase via our Web site, phone, or fax. Information we collect may include name, address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, and personal interests. In addition, NetTravel.com periodically sponsors contests and other promotions that may require additional information in order to participate.  

Back To Top   
   
What we do with this information   
  
The requests for information allow NetTravel.com to provide services you have requested or to enhance your experience while visiting us. The information that we collect during a purchase is necessary for us to fulfill your order, track the status of your order, and provide the best customer service possible. In addition to that it helps us understand our customers and their interests better. This is a way by which we can offer you the best.  
  
NetTravel.com assures you that it will not sell your private information to any outside company for its use in marketing or solicitation. The information we take from you is used to keep you updated with the latest and notify important announcement regarding important functionality changes to our website.  
  
NetTravel.com may also use customer information on a collective basis to understand our users better and to improve our services. Collective statistics may also be disclosed to potential advertisers and/or business partners. (For example, we may use an aggregate statistics, say, "25% of NetTravel.com visitors are from Washington", but we would never give away that "Mrs. Virginia Hughes, age 25,is from Washington" unless of course we had prior permission.)  

Back To Top  
   
The use of "cookies"   
  
Cookies are small information files stored on your hard drive by your browser that allows providing advanced features like personalization. NetTravel.com does use cookies but the ones we use do not contain any personal information. You may change your browser setting to disable cookies, if you wish. But please note that cookies must be enabled on your browser in order to purchase a membership.  

Back To Top   
   
Your consent   
  
By visiting and purchasing products through NetTravel.com's Web site, you give consent to the collection and use of the information described above by NetTravel.com. We may periodically modify our privacy policy and will post any changes on this page so you can always be up to date on the information we collect and how we use it.   

Back To Top
